ALLISON KLINGER: Hello, my name is Allison at Western Art Glass in Salt Lake City.
I am the owner of the store here.
I teach a variety of classes.
I carry tons of stained glass, lots of fun stuff.
I carry all types of tools, supplies, pattern books.
We teach so many classes.
Working with glasses is so much fun that once you start it leads to another method, okay?
There's beginning stained glass.
There is leaded glass.
There is stepping stones.
There's fused glass, which means it's made in a kiln, and you actually fuse the glass together and create your own glass, make bowls, plates, platters.
There's torched beads you can make out of glass.
And today, I get to play with foiled glass.
I get to play with stepping stone glass.
In fact, I get to do whatever I want.
So you should get involved.
You'll fall in love with it and, either which way, go to your local stained glass store.
If you don't have one, look it up in the phonebook under glass, stained and leaded, or look up on the phonebook, glass--or up on the Internet for stained glass.
And if you don't have one locally, drive to one.
It will all be worth it.
So check it out.